tryhydroxatone.com 2014-07-02

# Privacy Policy

Effective Date: January 21, 2014

Hydroxatone, LLC ("Hydroxatone", "we" "us") has developed this Privacy Policy which details important information regarding the use and disclosure of user information collected on this website and other websites owned and operated by Hydroxatone as well as through email or interactive and mobile applications of Hydroxatone ("Hydroxatone Applications"). Hydroxatone provides this Privacy Policy to help you make an informed decision about whether to use or participate in the Hydroxatone Applications.

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to Hydroxatone's [Terms of Use](https://sputnik.acmgaces.com/legal.php?brand=hydroxatone&type=terms_of_use&country=domestic). Each time that you access or use Hydroxatone Applications you signify that you have read, understand, and agree to be bound by the Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy, you must discontinue using the Hydroxatone Applications.

**Registration.** We will collect personal information from you when you place an order for any Hydroxatone products and services (collectively, "Products"). We may also collect information from you when you interact with our Hydroxatone Applications, interact with other users, and use various features of our Hydroxatone Applications.

**Surveys and Promotions.** From time-to-time we may request information from you and other users via surveys, contests or sweepstakes. Participation in these surveys, contests or sweepstakes is completely voluntary so you and other users have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and address), and demographic information (such as zip code). Contact information may be used to notify the winners, award prizes and file winner's information as required by law. Survey information will be used for the purpose(s) of the survey, including the monitoring or improvement of the use and satisfaction of Hydroxatone Applications.

**Information Shared With Social Networking Sites.**  You may be given the option to link your account on third party social networking services so that you can share your information and/or to comment on Hydroxatone products and services or take advantage of other features of Hydroxatone Applications.  In that case, the authentication of your login credentials is conducted through that third party social networking service provider.  If you choose to share information from the Hydroxatone Applications through any social networking service provider you should review the privacy policies of that social networking service provider.  You should make sure that you are comfortable with the information your third party social networking service provider may make available to us by visiting those services' privacy policies and/or modifying your privacy settings directly with those services.  By authorizing the social networking service provider to provide this information to us we reserve the right to use, transfer, assign, sell, share and provide access to such information in the same ways described in this Privacy Policy. 

**Information You Provide About a Third Party.** If you send someone else a communication from the Hydroxatone Applications, such as sending an invitation to a friend, the information you provide (names, e-mail addresses, etc.) is used to facilitate the communication and is not used for any other marketing purpose unless we obtain consent from that person or we explicitly say otherwise. Please be aware that when you use any send-to-a-friend functionality on the Hydroxatone Applications, your e-mail address may be included in the communication sent to your friend.

**User Generated Content.** Please remember that any information you disclose while participating on the Hydroxatone Applications, including our public forums ("Interactive Forums"), becomes public information and is subject to redistribution by Hydroxatone and others who gain access. Therefore, you should exercise caution and discretion when deciding to disclose your personal information in a submission or posting. There is no expectation of privacy when playing, posting, or otherwise participating on the Hydroxatone Applications or in the Interactive Forums. If you post content, such as messages, photos and videos, please be aware that any personally identifiable information contained in such content is accessible to registered users or visitors to that Hydroxatone Application or Community and we have no control over how those users may use your personally identifiable information. We have the right, but not the obligation, to monitor any activity and content associated with the interactive areas on our Hydroxatone Applications and Interactive Forums. We reserve the right to take action in connection with any content we deem to be inappropriate. Please review our [Terms of Use](https://sputnik.acmgaces.com/legal.php?brand=hydroxatone&type=terms_of_use&country=domestic) for more information regarding your appropriate use of these areas.

**Supplemental Information.** We may from time to time supplement information you give us with information from other sources, such as information to validate or update your address or other demographic and lifestyle information. We use this information to help us maintain the accuracy of the information we collect, to target our communications so that we can inform you of products, services and offers that may be of interest, and for internal business analysis or other business purposes.

**Information Collected Through Technology.** In addition to any personal information or other information that you choose to submit to us, we and our third-party service providers may use a variety of technologies such as cookies, pixel tags and web beacons, browser analysis tools, and web server logs. As you use our Hydroxatone Applications, your browser and devices communicate with servers operated by us, our business partners and services providers to coordinate and record the interactivity and fill your requests for services and information ("Usage Information"). We collect many different types of information from cookies and other technologies. For example, we may collect information from the devices you use to access our Hydroxatone Applications, your operating system type or mobile device model, browser type, domain, and other system settings, as well as the language your system uses and the country and time zone of your device. Browsers routinely send these types of information to web servers. In addition, we collect your IP address or other unique identifier ("Device Identifier") for your computer or other device used to access the Hydroxatone Applications (any, a "Device"). A Device Identifier is a number that is automatically assigned to the device used to access the Hydroxatone Applications, and our computers identify your device by its Device Identifier. We may also collect information about the website you were visiting before you came to our Hydroxatone Applications and the website you visit after you leave our Hydroxatone Applications, if this information is supplied to us by your browser. We may use this Usage Information for a variety of purposes, including to enhance or otherwise improve the Hydroxatone Applications.

The information from cookies and related technology is stored in web server logs and also in web cookies kept on your computers or mobile devices, which are then transmitted back to our Sites by your computers or mobile devices. These servers are operated and the cookies managed by us, our business partners or our service providers. For example, when you visit the Hydroxatone Applications, we and our service providers may place cookies on your computers or mobile devices. Cookies allow us to recognize you when you return, track and target your interests in order to provide a customized experience. They also help us provide a customized experience and help us to detect certain kinds of fraud. A "cookie" is a small amount of information that a web server sends to your browser that stores information about your account, your preferences, and your use of the Sites. Some cookies contain serial numbers that allow us to connect your activity with the Hydroxatone Applications with other information we store about you in your profile or as related to your interactions with the Hydroxatone Applications.

Some cookies are temporary, whereas others may be configured to last longer. "Session" cookies are temporary cookies used for various reasons, such as to manage page views. Your browser usually erases session cookies once you exit your browser. "Persistent" cookies are more permanent cookies that are stored on your computers or mobile devices even beyond when you exit your browser. We use persistent cookies for a number of purposes, such as retrieving certain information you have previously provided.

Flash cookies, known as local shared objects, are data files placed on a Device via the Adobe Flash plug-in that may be built-in to or downloaded by you to your Device to personalize your visit. Our third-party service providers also may use Flash cookies to collect and store Usage Information. Flash cookies are different from standard browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and how data is stored. Cookies may be used for many purposes, including, without limitation, remembering you and your preferences and tracking your visits to our web pages. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a persistent or session cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off such cookies through your browser settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. However, cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies, please click <http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html>. If you choose to disable cookies on your Device, some features of the Sites may not function properly. If you click on ads that appear on our Hydroxatone Applications, our advertising partners may also transmit cookies to your Device. This Privacy Policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers; each advertiser's use of cookies is covered by that advertiser's own privacy policy.

Pixel tags and web beacons are tiny graphic images placed on website pages or in our emails that allow us to determine whether you have performed specific actions, and may be used to track your interactions with those messages, such as when you receive, open or click a link in an email message from us. When you access these pages or open email messages, the pixel tags and web beacons generate a notice of that action to us, or our service providers. These tools allow us to measure response to our communications and improve our web pages and promotions.

We may use HTML5, another form of collection, in our apps for the iphone or iPad (and any other Apple iOS device). HTML5 is another form of collection, tracking and storage that does not rely on traditional browser cookies. Like Flash cookies, HTML5 cookies can be used to track users across websites but are not stored in browers' cookie files. To our knowledge there is currently no known way for a user of a mobile device to remove HTML5 tracking and storage.

We sometimes use embedded scripts which are programming codes designed to collect information about your interactions with the Hydroxatone Applications, such as the links you click on. The code is temporarily downloaded onto your Device from our web server or a third party service provider, is active only while you are connected to the Hydroxatone Applications, and is deactivated or deleted thereafter.

In many cases, the information we collect using cookies and other tools is used in non-identifiable ways, without any reference to personal information. For example, we use information we collect about Hydroxatone Application users to optimize our services and understand traffic and usage patterns. In other cases, we associate the information we collect using cookies and related technologies with Personal Information. Whenever we associate Usage Information or a Device Identifier with your personal information, we will treat it as personal information.

**Third Party Analytics Technologies.** We use third parties' analytic and other tools to better understand who is using the Hydroxatone Applications, how people are using the Hydroxatone Applications and how to improve the effectiveness of the Hydroxatone Applications, and to help us serve more targeted content and advertising to you. Those third party companies may use cookies, pixel tags or other technologies to collect and store anonymous information such as time of visit, pages visited, time spent on each page of the Hydroxatone Applications, Device Identifiers, type of operating system and browser used and other web sites you may have visited. We do not have access to, nor control over, third parties' use of cookies or other tracking technologies. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third parties to see your options for opting out of their use of such devices. If you would like more information regarding which third party companies we use to provide these services who may be serving cookies or other tracking tools on our Hydroxatone Applications or want to know more about what your choices are about not having this anonymous collected or used by these companies, please click here.

**Our Business Relationship.** When you provide us with information in connection with a particular activity or otherwise sign up for our services or provide your contact information, including an email address or telephone number in connection with that activity, product or service, you agree that this action constitutes a purchase or inquiry establishing a business relationship with us. You expressly consent to our communicating with you future information about Hydroxatone using the information you provided to us. You also attest that you have the legal authority over any telephone number you provide to us and can provide us with the authorization to contact you. This means we may contact you, in person or by recorded message, by e-mail, telephone and/or mobile telephone number (including use of automated dialing equipment), text (SMS) message, or any other means of communication that your wireless or other telecommunications device may be capable of receiving.

**Connecting with the Hydroxatone Applications and Interactive Forums.** By posting to our Interactive Forums, you give us permission to capture and store information you provide us and display it to other users in order to provide the best possible experience on the Hydroxatone Applications. Therefore, you should exercise caution and discretion when deciding to disclose your personal information in a submission or posting. There is no expectation of privacy in the Interactive Forums and we have no control over how those users may use your personally identifiable information.

**Service Providers.** We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Hydroxatone Applications or administer activities on our behalf. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes.

**Third Party Advertising.** Third parties advertise offers on Hydroxatone Applications and in the course of serving those offers, these third-parties use technology to send, directly to your Device, the advertisements and links that appear on Hydroxatone Applications. They automatically receive your Device Identifier when this happens and use tracking technologies to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements, to personalize the advertising content and for accounting purposes. These third parties may also use combined information about your visits to our Hydroxatone Applications and other sites in order to provide advertisements about related goods and services that may be of particular interest to you. When you click on a third party advertisers' link, you will enter the third party's site. This Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such advertisers or third party ad networks. You should consult the respective privacy policies of any advertisers on Hydroxatone Applications to see your options for opting out of their use of such tracking devices. In addition, some of the ad serving networks may be members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers a single location to opt out of ad targeting from member companies. If you opt-out of receiving targeted ads on Hydroxatone Applications from ad servers and ad networks, you may continue to receive advertising and promotional messages after you opt-out, but it will not be customized or personalized to you based on your use of our Hydroxatone Applications and/or third party websites. If you would like more information about advertisers' use of tracking technologies and about your option not to accept the cookies used to track your activities, you can go to <http://www.networkadvertising.org/>. If you would like to learn more about how interest-based information is collected, whether the companies we use are part of an industry network regarding behavioral advertising and to know your choices about not having information used in this manner you can go to <http://www.aboutads.info/>.

**Strategic Partners.** From time to time we may enter into a relationship with another company that is not owned by or affiliated with us to provide additional features on the Hydroxatone Applications. These special relationships may include business partners, sponsors and co-branded Hydroxatone Applications (referred to here as "co-branded pages"). Any information, including personally identifiable information that you provide on one of these co-branded pages will be shared with these third party partners. Since these third parties will use your information in accordance with their own privacy practices, you should check their website for information regarding their privacy policies.

**Other Uses:** We may use your personal information to contact you about services on our Hydroxatone Applications for which you have expressed an interest, for example, if you have contacted customer service or made an inquiry.

**Transactional Notices.** We may send you announcements and emails from time to time relating to your account. These include emails such as order confirmations, customer service notifications or responses or when the delivery of a product is delayed. You may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature.

**Electronic Offers and Promotional Messages.** We may also send you updates and communications about our products and services or other messages, such as newsletters, changes to features of the Service, or special offers. If you do not want to receive such messages, you may opt out by contacting customer service at 1-800-672-2259. You also will be given the opportunity, in any promotional email or text message that we send to you to opt out of receiving such messages in the future. Follow the unsubscribe instructions included in each email or click "STOP" on a mobile text. It may take up to 10 days for us to process an opt-out email or mobile text request.

**Direct Marketing.** Your personal information may be provided to the Hydroxatone family of companies or our affiliated companies or third parties for their own direct marketing purposes. If you do not wish to receive direct mail marketing materials from us or share your information to any third party for direct mail marketing purposes, you may opt out of such activities by contacting us by any of the methods provided in the **Contact Us** paragraph below. Please note that even if you opt out of receiving promotional direct mail offers, we may continue to send you service notifications that are related to your account(s) and other products and services you have requested or in which you are currently enrolled by direct mail.

**Telemarketing.** If you have given us your telephone number, when making an inquiry or registering with us or when ordering Products from us, we may use the telephone number you provided to reach out to you to follow up on your order, including follow-up renewals and marketing. Your telephone number may be provided to Hydroxatone family of companies or our affiliated companies or third parties for their own direct marketing purposes. If you would prefer not to receive marketing phone calls from us, send an email to [support@Hydroxatone.com](mailto:support@Hydroxatone.com) with "Do Not Call" in the subject line or call customer care at 1-800-672-2259 or ask to be placed on our do not call list when you receive a call from us. Please note that even if you opt out of receiving promotional telephone calls, we may continue to call you for issues that are related to your account(s), orders, unpaid invoices, or other Products you have requested.

**Feedback.** All comments, feedback or materials submitted by you to Hydroxatone including feedback, testimonials, images, reviews, questions, comments, suggestions or ideas (collectively, "Feedback"), shall be received and treated by us on a non-confidential and unrestricted basis. Hydroxatone will be free to use, display, perform, distribute, copy, adapt, and promote, in any medium now known or later developed, without compensation to you, the Feedback along with all ideas, concepts, know-how, techniques or methodologies contained in such Feedback, for any purpose whatsoever, including without limitation, developing, marketing and selling products and services incorporating such Feedback. You agree that in submitting Feedback, it will not violate any right of any third party, including any confidentiality, copyright, trademark, privacy or other personal or intellectual property or proprietary rights, and will not cause injury to any person or entity. You further agree that no Feedback you submit will be or contain libelous or otherwise unlawful, threatening, abusive or obscene material, or contain viruses, commercial solicitations, or any form of "spam". If you wish to access any personal information which may be associated with this information you can contact us at [privacy@hydroxatone.com](mailto:privacy@hydroxatone.com).

**Legal Matters; Safety.** We may, without your consent, access and disclose your information, any communications sent or received by you (including, without limitation, the contents of any communication in the Interactive Forums), and any other information that we may have about you or your account as may be permitted or required by law (including, but not limited to, court order or subpoena), or to prevent or investigate suspected fraud, violations of our Terms of Use, or activity that appears to us to be illegal or may expose us to legal liability. Additionally, we may disclose your information and/or communications in situations that we believe to be emergencies involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person or property if we believe that your information in any way relates to that threat or when we believe your conduct on the Hydroxatone Applications or in the Interactive Forums is inappropriate and inconsistent with generally accepted norms of behavior.

**Sale or Transfer of Business or Assets.** In the event that we, or any of our businesses, are sold or disposed of as a going concern, whether by merger, sale of assets or otherwise, or in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership, personally identifiable information of our users may be one of the assets sold or merged in connection with that transaction. Such information may also need to be disclosed in connection with a commercial transaction where we or any one of our businesses are seeking financing, investment, support or funding. In such transactions, personal information will be subject to the promises made in any pre-existing privacy policy in effect when the information was obtained.

You may access any personal information you provide to us, correct or modify any such personal information, or direct us to make no further use of your personal information. To do so, please send an email with your request to [support@Hydroxatone.com](mailto:support@Hydroxatone.com). If you chose to deactivate your account with us, we may still retain certain information associated with your account for analytical purposes and record keeping integrity, as well as to prevent fraud, resolve disputes, enforce our [Terms of Use](https://sputnik.acmgaces.com/legal.php?brand=hydroxatone&type=terms_of_use&country=domestic) or other policies, take actions we deem necessary due to technical and legal requirements and constraints related to the security, integrity and operation of our Hydroxatone Applications. In addition, if certain information has already been provided to third parties as described in this Privacy Policy, retention of that information will be subject to those third parties' policies.

You may remove your information from our database so as not to receive future communications or to close your account or opt out of our sharing information with third parties for marketing purposes by emailing us at [support@Hydroxatone.com](mailto:support@Hydroxatone.com). If you prefer not to receive electronic promotional communications, you can also opt-out by following the unsubscribe instructions included in each communication.

Please note that changes may not be effective immediately. In each event, you must clearly indicate the information that you wish to have changed or clearly indicate that you wish to have your personally identifiable information removed from our database. We will endeavor to comply with your request as soon as reasonably possible. Note that despite any request for removal of or change to personally identifiable information, we may need to retain certain information for record keeping purposes and there may also be residual information that will remain within our databases and other records, which will not be removed or changed and we may still retain certain information associated with your account for analytical purposes and record keeping integrity, as well as to prevent fraud, resolve disputes, enforce our [Terms of Use](https://sputnik.acmgaces.com/legal.php?brand=hydroxatone&type=terms_of_use&country=domestic) or other policies, take actions we deem necessary due to technical and legal requirements and constraints related to the security, integrity and operation of our Hydroxatone Applications. In addition, if certain information has already been provided to third parties as described in this Privacy Policy, retention of that information will be subject to those third parties' policies. Finally, we are not responsible for informing third parties (including without limitation our third party service providers or strategic partners) with whom we have already shared your personally identifiable information of any changes requested pursuant to this section, or for removing information from or causing information to be removed from the databases or records of such entities.

**Links to other Site and Interactive Forums.** To the extent hyperlinks may be utilized to access external or third party sites and Interactive Forums, you should be aware that these external or third party site and Interactive Forums are not controlled by us and, therefore, are not subject to this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you check the privacy policies of each such site and community to determine how your personal information will be utilized by their proprietors.

**Security.** Please keep in mind that no data transmission over the Internet, wireless transmission or electronic storage of information can be guaranteed to be 100% secure and therefore we cannot ensure the security of any information you transmit to us, and your use of the Hydroxatone Applications indicates that you are willing to assume this risk.

**A Note To International Users.** The Hydroxatone Applications are hosted in the United States. If you are using the Hydroxatone Applications from outside the United States, by providing your information to the Hydroxatone Applications, you are consenting to the transfer of your information to the United States for processing and maintenance in accordance with this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service. You are also consenting to the application of United States federal, and New Jersey state law in all matters concerning the Hydroxatone Applications.

**Children's Privacy.** Hydroxatone does not knowingly collect or solicit Personal Information from individuals under 13 years of age. If you are under 13 years of age, you should not provide Personal Information on the Hydroxatone Applications. In the event that we learn that we have collected Personal Information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [privacy@hydroxatone.com](mailto:privacy@hydroxatone.com).

**Your California Privacy Rights (As provided by California Civil Code Section 1798.83).** California's "Shine the Light" law, Civil Code section 1798.83, requires certain businesses to respond to requests from California customers asking about the business' practices related to disclosing personal information to third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. Alternately, such businesses may have in place a policy not to disclose personal information of customers to third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes if the customer has exercised an option to opt-out of such information-sharing. We have such a policy in place. If you do not want us to share your Personal Information with other companies so that they can send you direct mail offers about their products and services, please contact us by any of the methods provided in the **Contact Us** paragraph below. California customers may request further information about our approach to this law by writing to us at the address provided in the "Contact Us" section.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy.** We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most recent version of the Privacy Policy will always be posted on our Sites, with the "Effective Date" posted at the top of the Policy. We may revise and update this Privacy Policy if our practices change, as technology changes, or as we add new Hydroxatone Applications or change existing ones. If we make any material changes to our Privacy Policy or how we handle your personal information, you will know because the Effective Date of the Privacy Policy will change. By using our Hydroxatone Applications after the Effective Date, you are deemed to consent to our then-current privacy policy.

**Disputes.** If you choose to visit the Hydroxatone Applications your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy, and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, resolution of disputes, and application of the laws of the United States, and the State of New Jersey.

**No Rights of Third Parties.** This Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any personal information relating to users of the Hydroxatone Applications.

**Questions About Privacy Policy or Hydroxatone Applications.** If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or the practices of the Hydroxatone Applications, please email us at [privacy@hydroxatone.com](mailto:privacy@hydroxatone.com).

**Contact Us.** Please contact us by emailing queries to [support@Hydroxatone.com](mailto:support@Hydroxatone.com) or calling 1-800-672-2259 or writing to us at Hydroxatone, LLC., P.O. Box 1366, Hoboken, NJ 07030

Last Updated: January 21, 2014

DoubleClick | <http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>  
---|---  
Google | <http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>  
Flurry | <http://www.flurry.com/about-us/legal/privacy.html>  
Kount | <http://www.kount.com/legal/privacy-policy>  
Link Trust | <http://www.linktrust.com/privacy-policy/>  
Site Scout | <http://www.sitescout.com/privacy/>  
The Search Agency | <http://www.thesearchagency.com/privacy-policy.html>
